以下是《无耻家庭》前情提要
我马上要生了
I have baby soon.
我不能工作
I cannot work.
他必须照顾我跟孩子
He must take care of me and baby.
天呐
Oh, my god.
现在这是个全新的我
I'm a different person.
我受够了按别人说的生活了
I'm done living the way other people want me to live.
你男朋友在吗
Is your boyfriend here?
该死
Damn.
你知道你快死了  对吧
You know you're dying, right?
不会  我还没准备死呢
Nope, not ready to punch my ticket yet.
你老婆的羊水破了  我们走吧
Your wife's water broke. Let's go.
-去哪儿  -医院
- Go where? - The hospital.
那个贱人被搞大肚子也不是我的错
It's not my fault the bitch got knocked up.
到本周一  我已经戒毒三周年了
Three years sober this Monday.
那真是太棒了  罗比
That's really great, Robbie.
-那简直好极了  -恭喜
- Yeah, that's excellent. - Congrats.
谢谢你这么帮我
Thank you so much for doing all this.
真的  我不知道该怎么报答你
You know, I wish I could think of a way to repay you.
我相信你会想到的
I'm sure you'll think of something.
这是外婆
Here's grandma.
真是个小天使
He's such a little angel.
小凯  她想留下孩子
Kev, she wants to keep him.
我不想失去他  小维
I don't wanna lose him, V.
他还是你的儿子  你的孩子
He'll still be your son, your boy.
她来抚养
Her responsibility.
我们还可以一起玩
You know, we can still do stuff together.
是的  很好
Yeah, great. Cool.
就像朋友一样出去玩
Hang out. Like friends do.
-回头再说  -好的
- Talk to you later. - Yeah.
-他脸上的是什么  -天呐
- What's on his face? - Oh, my god.
他吸了我的可卡因
He got into my coke.
你将被软禁在家  等待后续通知
You will be under house arrest until further notice.
如果你企图离开这里
If you attempt to leave the residence,
无线电波发射器会给我们警局的电脑中心
a radio frequency transmitter will send an alert,
然后你麻烦就大了
and you will be in deep shit.
无耻家庭
第四季第九集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  扎克不渣     重案组李Sir     落     君君
■
翻译：  姚小事     爱卿遛小鸟     拉图     Greentie
时间轴：  aaaBao      JimmyBeck
■
校对：  Greentie      落
后期： 孤帆          总监： 落
■
还有41分钟我就可以出门了
41 minutes until I'm allowed out.
我都快闻到空气中的那股垃圾和尿骚味儿了
I can almost taste the garbage and urine-scented air.
我把账单过了一遍
Look, I went through the bills.
取消了有线电视  卡尔只能忍着了
Cancelled cable. Carl will just have to deal.
我应该还可以继续从学校食堂顺食物回来
Figure I can keep sneaking food from the cafeteria.
而且我还有笔助学贷款就要下来了
And then I have a student loan check coming.
我想应该够付
You know, I think that should cover
下个月的房租水电了
next month's rent and power.
那你拿什么交学费
What'll you use for tuition?
我会想到法子的
I'll think of something.
可那是你读书的钱
But that money's for school.
是啊  不过当前解决暖气问题才是最重要的
Yeah, well, heat's a little more important right now.
不行  你可不能辍学  知道吗
No, you're not dropping out, okay?
我会找份工作  等我跟假释官报过到之后
I'm getting a job. I've got an interview
我就有个面试
right after I check in with my probation officer.
薪水还不错
Pay's not bad.
放心吧  我搞得定  我保证
I got this. It'll work out, I promise.
好吧
Okay.
你今晚回来睡吗
You staying here tonight?
是的  明天上午没课
Yeah, no morning classes tomorrow.
咱们去叫小家伙起床吧
Let's go wake up the little guy.
好的
Sure.
别挡道  我要上厕所
Make way, I call crapper.
米奇怎么还在这里
Mickey's still here?
我他妈怎么知道
I don't fucking know.
早上好  小阳光
Morning, sunshine.
他肯定又做恶梦了
He must had another nightmare.
我去黛比的床下看看
I'll check under Debbie's bed.
干衣机里
Dryer?
我第一个就查看的那里
That's the first place I checked.
我不知道他还能去哪儿
I don't know where else he could be.
小家伙
Hey, buddy.
你找到一个好地方了
Hey, you found a comfy spot there?
要不要喝点果汁
Hey, how 'bout some juice?
-好的  -要来点果汁吗
- Yeah. - You want some juice?
没了  喝完了
No, we're all out.
你们能不能叫那个谁去商店
Hey, can you tell whoever's going to the store
买点儿鸡蛋和塔巴斯科辣酱油回来
to get some eggs and tabasco?
-你现在住这儿了  -跟老婆闹矛盾了
- You live here now? - Wife problems.
伊恩说可以让我打地铺
Ian said I could crash on the floor.
这里可不是收容所
This isn't a shelter.
可不是嘛  收容所可比你家好多了
No shit, shelter has better water pressure.
好了  小家伙  给你穿衣服了
All right, buddy, let's get you dressed.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
熬夜了
Late night?
工作到凌晨两点
Got outta work around 2:00.
也是
Right.
楼下还有咖啡吗
There any coffee downstairs?
有  还有
Yeah, yeah.
那个  米奇还待在这儿呢
So, uh, Mickey's still here.
没错
Yeah.
要待多久
For how long?
你真觉得这样好吗
Are you sure that's a good idea?
闻到咖啡香了
Mmm, coffee.
他已经昏迷18个小时了
He's been out 18 hours.
他还醒得过来吗
Is he ever gonna wake up?
我不是这方面的专家
I'm not a specialist.
可你是医生
You're a doctor.
住院医生而已
Resident.
你是医院里唯一肯来的医生了
You're the only one from the hospital who'd come.
我会尽量让他
I'd make him comfortable
在为数不多的日子里舒服点
for however much time he has left.
他时日无多了
It's not much.
就这样
That's it?
你就没有别的能做的了吗
There's nothing else you can do?
恐怕是这样
Afraid not.
你说过我给他检查完后你就...
You said after I examined him...
恰奇  去看电视
Chuckie, go watch tv.
没什么可看的
Nothing on.
那去给妈妈做个三明治
Then go make mommy a sandwich.
快点  快去做  快点
Come on, hop to it. Let's go.
别停啊
Don't stop.
就算你哭我也还是能射的
I can still come if you're crying.
咱们到了
Ah, there you go.
去了趟玩具反斗城
Made a run to Toys "R" Us.
我想这玩意儿应该能让你的小弟弟忙活一会儿
Figured it would help keep your little bro occupied.
那个  他才三岁
Uh, yeah, you know, he's three,
所以  一个纸箱子或是一串钥匙
so, uh, he's fine with a cardboard box
已经够他玩了
or a set of keys.
看起来他倒是挺满意的
Looks like a satisfied customer to me.
现在轮到让大哥哥也满意一下了
Now it's big brother's turn.
我有课
I got class.
那也不至于抽不出15分钟吧
Not for another 15 minutes.
我可没打算留你那么久呢
I don't plan on keeping you that long.
不行  我的意思是
No, I try to make a point
我不能搞我室友的马子  所以
of not banging my roommate's girlfriend, so...
可上次也没见你喊停啊
Didn't stop you last time.
-当时我在睡觉  -之后不就醒了
- I was asleep. - Until you weren't.
而且我们不算搞过
And we're not banging.
我还是处女呢
I'm a virgin.
不可能  我都听到你和朗干过好多回了
No, I-I've heard you and Ron go at it plenty of times.
我只让他走"后庭"
Backdoor only.
我想把第一次留给我未来的丈夫
I'm saving myself for my husband.
是吗  那要是你丈夫知道
Right, and how would your husband feel
你跟个AV女优一样随便会怎么想
about you having taken it in the seat like a porn star?
那你又为什么在上课之前还过来这里一趟
Why'd you stop by here before class?
承认吧  是因为你希望我在这里
Admit it, because you were hoping I'd be here.
借过
Excuse me, guys.
忘了拿《斯宾诺莎》了
Forgot my Spinoza.
对不起  听我解释
Hey, I'm--I'm so sorry. Just let me explain.
没关系  兄弟
It's okay, dude.
你不用对不起  我还得谢你呢
You don't need to be sorry. I owe you one.
我做梦都开始听见阿曼达使唤我了
I was starting to hear Amanda bark orders to me in my dreams.
所以我们  没事了
So we're-- we're cool?
让阿曼达口交最大的好处就是
The best part about getting a blow job from Amanda,
可以安静十分钟
ten minutes of silence.
快点  兄弟  上课别迟到
Come on, dude. Don't be late for class.
加拉格
Gallagher.
又能出门了真好
Good to be out of the house again.
你没惹什么麻烦吧
You staying out of trouble?
软禁在家不会惹什么麻烦
Not too much trouble you can get into on house arrest.
好吧  从今天开始你可以在
Mm-hmm, well, starting today you're allowed to be out
早八点到晚六点之间出门
8:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m.
-晚一分钟都不可以  六点整  明白了吗  -明白了
- Not 6:01，not 6:02. 6:00 p.m., you got that? - Yeah.
你已经缺席三次集会了  戴蒙
You missed three meetings, Damon.
我感冒了  没收到我的短信吗
I caught the flu. You ain't get my messages?
如果你错过宵禁
And if you miss curfew,
你就违反了假释的条件
you'll violate the terms of your probation,
你就回到监狱去
and you can go back to jail.
你有工作吗
You got a job?
正在找
I'm working on it.
假释的条件是
Terms of your probation
你在30天之内找到工作
require that you gain employment within 30 days.
我能给你介绍一个中介
I can give you the name of an agency.
我今天下午有个面试
I've got an interview this afternoon,
一份办公室的工作
an office job.
我以前就是做这个的
That's what I had before.
你上次吸毒是什么时候
When was the last time you used?
我被捕之后就没吸过了
Not since the night of my arrest.
有去戒毒互助会吗
Going to N.A.?
明天第一次集会
First meeting's tomorrow.
我需要出勤表证明你去了
I'll need verification that you attend.
给我个尿样
Just give me a urine sample,
就完事儿了
and we are done.
你还要看着  还是我自己来
You wanna watch or am I going stag this time?
怎么回事
What the--
你醒了
You're up.
感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
难闻死了
That smelt.
是香薰
Oh, incense.
叫"波斯香薰"
It's called Persian Spice.
我以为会像巴格达集市的
I was afraid it would stink like the toilet
厕所一样难闻  但是我觉得还挺好的
at a Baghdad Bazaar, but I think it's nice.
你喜欢吗
You like it?
教会音乐
Church music?
我让恰奇出去买些乳液
I just sent Chuckie out for some lotion.
给你按摩一下怎么样
Doesn't a massage sound nice?
我以前见过这场面
I've seen this before.
你想吃点东西吗  我给你准备点
You want a bite to eat? I could whip you up something.
好的
Okay.
临终关怀院
Hospice.
你肯定饿了
You must be hungry.
我不是要死的人
I'm not dying.
我知道这很艰难
I know this is hard.
我只想尽量让你舒适一点
I'm just trying to make you as comfortable as possible.
那就带我去艾莱柏
Then take me to the Alibi.
酒吧
The--the bar?
我在那就挺舒适的
I was always comfortable there.
你有最后想去的地方吗
Is there a final resting place you had in mind?
墓地
A cemetery?
网站说不要用这个词
The website said not to use that word.
我不是要死的人
I am not dying.
好的
Okay.
我给你弄点吃的
I am going to fix you something to eat.
我去厨房的时候你可以看看这个
Will you just look at this while I'm in the kitchen?
圣经
划出你最喜欢的赞美诗
Circle your favorite psalms.
别说话  写作业
No talking. Do your homework.
你得加热一下尾端
You gotta heat the end of it.
什么
What?
你在做一把小刀  对吧
You're making a shank, right?
你得先拿打火机烧一下尾端
You gotta heat the end of it with a lighter first.
用之前抹点屎
Then smear it in poop before you use it
就能引发感染了
so it causes infection.
我爸爸在高戒备男子监狱
My dad's at Stateville Correctional.
我去那里之前先练习一下
I'm practicing for when I'm there.
他们让你来多久了
How long they got you in here for?
昨天开始的  因为霸凌
Last day. Bullying.
我还要待两周
Got two weeks ahead of me.
不许说话
No talking.
贱人
Bitch.
别担心  我来摆平她
Don't worry. I'll take care of her.
谢谢你帮我拿东西
Thanks for helping me carry my stuff.
不客气  朋友不就是该互相帮忙嘛
Yeah, what are friends for?
你什么时候开始玩贝斯了
Since when do you play bass?
乔说挺好学的
Oh, Josh said it was easy to learn.
说实话
You know, if I'm honest,
我不是很喜欢迷幻舞曲
I don't really think I like trip-hop all that much,
但是这帮兄弟人不错
but these guys are fun to hang out with.
你一会儿想去
You wanna meet up after,
一边看《暮光之城:破晓》一边吐槽吗
Hate-watch Twilight: Breaking Dawn?
去不了  抱歉
Oh, uh, I can't. I'm sorry.
要上班
Work?
不是
No, I'm, um...
要去见个人
Getting together with somebody.
约会
A date?
别担心  没关系
No worries. That's fine.
-我不在乎  -是吗
- I don't care. - Oh, you don't?
当然了  大家都有约会
No! Everyone has dates.
我也有
I have dates too.
好吧  我们只是在她上班之前
Oh, okay, well, we're just going bowling
打打保龄球
before her shift starts.
她在保龄球馆上班吗
She works at the bowling alley?
不是  比萨店
No, pizza place.
西玛  她才开始在那里上班
Seema. She just starting working there.
我培训的她  我们是这么认识的
I trained her. That's how we met.
真浪漫
Mm, how romantic.
真不错
Sounds nice.
你把她怎么了
What did you do to her?
往她咖啡里下了点药
Slipped a couple tabs of acid in her coffee.
你把斯宾塞老师变成僵尸了
You turned Mrs. Spencer into a zombie?
她只是眼前五颜六色而已  不会吃人
She's seeing colors, not gorging on human flesh.
-我叫邦妮  -卡尔
- I'm bonnie. - Carl.
来吧  卡尔  我们去搜刮她的钱包
Come on, Carl, let's raid her purse.
我之前听见她在厕所里哭
I heard her crying in the bathroom earlier,
所以我猜里面有不少郁乐复[抗抑郁药物]
So I'm guessing there's a bunch of zoloft in there.
你在干嘛
Hey, what you doing?
为工作做个短裤
Making shorts for work.
酒吧里吃嫩草的基佬
Trolls at the club get off
都有巴顿将军的性幻想  是吧
on the general patton fantasy, huh?
更喜欢海豹六队
More like Seal Team Six.
抱歉了
Excuse me.
他在哪
Where is he?
你他妈想干啥
The fuck you want?
你妹妹知道你在哪
So your sister knows where you are,
但是你孩子的母亲不能知道
but not mother of your child?
你什么时候回家
When you coming home?
我不回去
I'm not coming home.
五斤半
Seven pounds, six ounces.
你儿子的体重  如果你在意的话
Weight of your child, if you care.
还他妈挺重
Fat little fuck, is he?
我要竭尽所能
I do everything I can
不让他变成跟你一样的混蛋
so he doesn't turn into piece of shit like you.
你吹过那么多"正直"的好公民
Yeah, I'm sure you're gonna turn him
我相信你也一定能把他
Into a nice, upstanding citizen
教育得跟他们一样"正直"
since you've blown so many of them.
我们需要钱  买婴儿车  纸尿裤
We need money, stroller, changing pads.
去上班啊
Go to work.
去了  但是不够钱给瑞莎
I do, but it's not enough for Raisa.
瑞莎又他妈是谁
Who the fuck's Raisa?
其中一个姑娘
One of the girls.
她用脱毛膏的时候睡着了
She fell asleep while using nair.
现在阴部三度烫伤
She has third-degree burns on her pubis.
不能接客  所以让她来带孩子
She can't work, so she watches baby.
等下  难道我还要花钱
Hold on, I'm supposed to pay
让个妓女来给我带孩子
some whore on the D.L. to baby-sit?
不然你来带
You could watch him.
我有正事要做
Got better shit to do.
比如跟红毛小子搞基吗
Yeah, like what? Do ass fuck with orange boy?
说话小心点
Watch yourself.
你以为我怕你吗
You think you scare me?
你就是个巨型娘炮
You are 130 pounds of ukrainian pussy.
等你老爸出狱后
What's your father gonna say when he gets out of jail
我告诉他你每天都忙着跟人搞基
and I tell him you spend every day with orange boy
你觉得他会怎么做
rubbing your dicks together?
他会把你给阉了
He's gonna cut yours off
然后把你那话儿塞到你男朋友菊花里
and shove it up boyfriend's anus,
你不是最喜欢那里了吗
right where you like it.
明天给我五百块  不然我就打给他
$500 tomorrow or I call him.
你想知道你儿子的名字吗
Even want to know your son's name?
操你妈
Fuck you.
这就是他的名字
That's his name.
你之前有卖过家具吗
So have you ever worked in furniture before?
没有  但如果我能卖杯子
No, but trust me if I can sell cups,
那就什么都能卖
I can sell anything.
我们生产的是用来保护沙发的
Well, we manufacture waterproof polypropylene covers
防水塑料膜
that protect sofas and loveseats.
-如果你养宠物就很适用  -有孩子也一样吧
- Great if you have pets. - Or kids, I bet.
我有五个弟弟妹妹
I have five brothers and sisters.
真希望我早几年就买这个
I wish I'd bought one of these years ago.
这样吧  给你一套带回去
You know what, bring one of these home, okay?
拿着
Here.
总得要了解自己卖的东西吧
You gotta know what product you're selling, right?
当然了  谢谢
Absolutely. Thanks.
你现在只要帮我
Yeah, you know, actually I just need you
把这个表格填完
to, um, complete the application
然后我就能和我的推荐信一起
before I can send it up to Mr. Garrett
-送去给加瑞特先生了  -我填完了
- with my recommendation. - I did.
你少填了一项
Oh, you missed a box.
"你是否有过犯罪记录"
"Have you ever been convicted of a felony?"
这个表要很认真地填
You just got to dot all the "I"s
所以...
and cross all the "T"s, so...
谢谢
Thanks.
那...
So...
只是个小意外罢了
It was a small drug thing.
错的时间
I was around somebody
出现在了错的地方
that I shouldn't have been at the wrong time.
谁都可能碰上这种事
It coulda happened to anyone.
这是我唯一一次犯法
It's the only time I've ever been in trouble with the law.
我从上一份工作里积累了不少经验
I got a lot of really good experience from my last job.
升职得可快了
They promoted me really fast.
我们...
Uh, you know, we will, um...
我们再联系吧
We will be in touch.
我以前是他们那里业绩最好的
I became one of their top salespeople.
谢谢
Thank you.
老爸
Dad?
我做了你最爱吃的
I made your favorite.
干炸牛排加土豆泥和...
Chicken fried steak with mashed potatoes and grav--
我靠
God. Oh, fuck.
靠
Fuck.
老爸
Dad?
Dad.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
去艾莱伯酒吧
Alibi.
艾莱伯酒吧
Alibi?
你现在的状态不能到处跑
You--you are in no condition to go anywhere.
-我很好  -拜托  别这样
- I'm--I'm fine. - Oh, come on, come on.
-外面很冷  -我好得很
- It's freezing out. - I'm fine!
放开我
Get off of me!
停
Stop!
放开
No.
你看利亚姆用橡皮泥捏了一个你
Look what Liam made, a play-doh you.
还带着烟呢
There's even a little cigarette.
你能呼吸吗  能用那个呼吸吗
Can you breathe? Can you breathe with that?
听着  我很感谢你
Listen, uh, I really appreciate you, uh,
感谢你帮我带孩子什么的
Looking out for my-- my brother and all.
但我现在不想找女朋友
Um, I'm not really looking for a girlfriend here.
你真可爱
That's cute.
什么可爱
Well, what's--what's cute?
你觉得我想找男朋友吗
You think I want a boyfriend?
是啊...我觉得...
Well... Yeah, I mean, you, uh...
你把冰箱上朗的名字换成了我的
You replaced Ron's name with mine on the mini fridge.
利普专属
我只是不想让他
Yeah, I wanted to make sure
把我给你做的面给吃了
he didn't take The mac and cheese I made for you.
好吧
Oh, sure.
但这些事
But, uh, all these services
我可不是白做的
don't come for free.
起来
Come on.
什么
Sorry?
知道什么叫"Quid pro quo"吗
Familiar with the term "Quid pro quo"?
知道  那是...
Yeah, yeah, that's, uh...
拉丁语里"等价交换"的意思吧
That's latin for "Lick mine, and I'll lick yours," Right?
家长会的时候  你要装成我男朋友
Need you to meet my mom and dad for parents' weekend.
去见我父母
Pretend we're together.
就这样  就收拾收拾吃个晚餐
That's it? Just clean up for a dinner?
不  不要收拾
No, no clean up.
你穿上那件
In fact, wear that shirt
印满"操"字的衣服
with all the "Fucks" on it.
我父母在我三岁的时候
My parents started me on violin lessons
就让我学小提琴
when I was three.
12岁就开始准备SAT
S.A.T. Prep when I was 12.
我是个活生生的好学生范例
I'm a walking stereotype.
你瞧  我居然读了数学专业
For christ sakes, I'm a math major.
如果你父母不管你的话
You know, you--you could do a lot worse
你的生活可能会更糟
than parents that give a shit.
不行  现在是时候让他们知道
No, it's time my mom and dad know
我是不会像我姐姐一样
that I'm not gonna be programmed for med school
顺着他们去学医的
like my older sister.
我得好好吓吓他们
I need to scare the living shit out of them.
你愿意吗
So you in?
我们告诉他们利亚姆是我的孩子怎么样
How about we tell them Liam's my kid?
女士们先生们  我们对列车的晚点深感抱歉
Ladies and gentlemen, we apologize for the delay.
预计很快就会恢复正常
Should be moving shortly.
抱歉  车坏了吗
Hi, sorry. Is there a problem?
很快就能修好
Should have the train up and running soon.
多快
Uh, how soon?
我20分钟内得到家
I gotta be home in 20 minutes.
等等
Wait!
出租车
Taxi!
下班了
Off duty.
去后院区要多少钱
How much to back of the yards?
下班了
Off duty.
我是不会下车的
I am not getting out of this cab.
20到25块吧
Ugh, 20, 25.
我有12块  能开多远就多远
I got 12. Take me as far as you can.
我得跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
来啦  老兄  恭喜啊
Hey, there he is. Congratulations, man.
-酒水算店里请  -为什么
- Drink on the house. - What for?
庆祝你家孩子的出生啊
The birth of your child.
没错  我家孩子最近也出生了
Yeah, my kid just popped out too.
不过我岳母不肯让我来抚养他
But my mother in law won't let me raise him.
-你可真幸运  -对了  你老婆在楼上呢
- Lucky you. - Hey, your wife's upstairs.
我才懒得看那个贱货呢
I'm not looking at that fucking hosebag.
你就这样说你儿子他妈啊
Nice way to talk about the mother of your child.
她的奶子真是巨大
Her tits are enormous.
花点钱去爽一下绝对物超所值
Definitely worth the price of admission.
汤米  他可不想听
Tommy, he doesn't want to hear
你花钱干他老婆的事
about you going balls deep on his wife.
闭嘴吧你
Shut the fuck up.
我要楼上生意的分红
I need my cut from the business upstairs, please.
好吧  就在这呢
All right. I got it right here.
只有几百块
There's only a couple hundred bucks here.
是的  除掉了开销
Yeah, after expenses.
除了床单和堕胎费还有什么开销
What expenses other than sheets and abortions?
首先是租金  以及其他设备
Uh, rent for one. Utilities.
这鬼地方是你的
You own the fucking place.
是的  所以我开了个优惠价
Yeah, and I give us a very fair deal.
我需要500块  小凯
I need 500 bucks, Kev.
500块  我可没有  老兄
500? Well, I don't have it, man.
你是我见过的最差劲的皮条客
You are the worst fucking pimp I've ever seen.
这话算是某种侮辱吗
Is that supposed to be some kind of insult?
我以为你忙着和米奇玩过家家呢
Thought you were busy playing house with Mickey.
他老婆来了一趟
His wife stopped by.
带着他们的孩子  他不会有事吧
with their kid. Is he gonna be okay?
米奇吗  我他妈怎么知道
Mickey? How the hell should I know?
是宝宝
The baby.
考虑到他是被一个
Oh, considering he's being cared for
20岁的俄国妓女照顾着
by a 20 year old russian whore,
-目前还算好吧  -外面冻死了
- could be worse. - It's freezing out.
她只给他裹了一条薄裤  就把他抱过去了
She brought him by our house in nothing but a onesie.
这里是利亚姆穿过的旧衣服
It's, uh, some of Liam's old stuff.
可以请你确保让他穿暖吗
You'll make sure he's bundled up?
利普怎么样了
How's Lip?
别跟米奇的老婆说你从哪儿得到这些的  好吗
Don't tell Mickey's wife where you got this, okay?
我不会说的
I won't.
利普在家吗
Is Lip at home?
有时在有时不在
Back and forth,
但大部分晚上都在的
But most nights yeah.
我必须去工作了
I gotta get to work.
-还有10个街区呢  -你看看计价器
- It's ten more blocks. - Look at the meter.
11块
$11.
我说了我有12块钱
I said I have 12.
1块是小费
A tip.
嘿  你他妈去哪儿了
Hey, where the hell have you been?
天呐
Jesus.
我去了你家  你不在
I went to your house, you weren't there.
我得上班了
My shift's starting.
你身上有钱吗
Look, you got any money on you?
就几块钱  怎么了
Few bucks. Why?
几块可不够
I need more than that.
用来干什么
What for?
我那个贱人老婆觉得我欠她的
My bitch of a wife thinks I owe her something.
好像我是唯一干过她的男人一样
Like I'm the only guy ever dropped a fucking load in her.
小伙子们
Boys.
想上车来兜兜风吗
Ride around the block?
你看我们像是一对出来卖身的基佬吗
We look like a couple fags for sale to you?
是的
Yes.
这里可不是梅西百货  贱逼
Well, this ain't Macy's, bitch.
不是看到的东西都能买
You ain't windowshopping.
你现在在男孩城里
You're in boystown,
站在一个叫"妖精尾巴"的酒吧外
Outside a bar called the fairy tail.
你为什么不快点滚
Why don't you fuck off
别等我打断你的脊椎
before I give you a broken spine
正好配上你那软弱的娘们儿手腕
To go along with that limp wrist?
滚蛋吧  傻逼娘炮
Yeah, get going, you fucking fruit!
他以为有钱就能买到一切吗
Thinks he can buy whatever he wants
就因为他戴劳力士表  开奔驰就了不起吗
'cause he's got a fucking Rolex and an Sclass.
你经常遇到这种事吗
That shit happen to you a lot?
每晚都会
Every night.
都是有钱人吗
From rich dudes?
我得工作了
Gotta get to work.
喂  喂  等下
Hey, hey, hold on.
跟你老板说  你今晚要请病假
Tell your boss you're going home sick tonight.
病假
Sick?
是  随便什么借口  跟他说你得了艾滋
Yeah, whatever. Tell him you got aids.
轻轨出故障了
El broke down.
你找到工作了吗
You, uh, get a job?
似乎挺有希望
It's looking good.
学校里怎么样
How's school?
说起来  很复杂
Yeah, it's, uh, complicated.
跟室友间有点问题
Roommate stuff.
助学贷款支票下来了
The school loan check came in though.
我们已经谈过那一点了
We already talked about that.
你要继续上学
You're staying in school.
我可以找到工作的  别担心
I got leads on jobs. Don't worry.
晚餐好啦
Dinner's ready!
那是曼迪吗
Is that Mandy?
是的  没错  她是来找伊恩的
Yeah, yeah, she dropped by looking for Ian.
-他上夜班  -我跟她说过了
- He works nights. - I told her that.
-他几小时内都不会回来的  -跟她说过了
- He won't be home for hours. - Told her that.
她不是有男朋友的吗
Doesn't she have a boyfriend?
他去工作了  上夜班
Look, he's at work. Night shift.
我去清洗一下  给小维留给位置
I'm gonna go clean up. Set a place for V.
她要过来
She's coming by.
-菲奥娜回来了吗  -是的
- Fiona home?  - Yeah.
你最近有见过伊恩吗
Hey, um, you seen Ian recently?
有  他今天去过我家  带了一些婴儿服
Yeah, came by today. Brought over some baby clothes.
你觉得他看起来没事吗
He seem okay to you?
我不知道他在搞什么  但看上去似乎没事
I don't know what he's on, but, yeah, I guess.
我很担心他
I'm worried about him.
他一直都紧绷着神经过日子
He's wound up so tight.
现在释放了也很正常
He's bound to uncork at some point.
那可能更健康  你好  黛比
It's probably healthy. Hey, Debbie.
我们晚餐是  食堂肉饼
Hey, we got, uh, cafeteria meatloaf for dinner.
如果你蘸上足够多的番茄酱的话
And if you douse it in enough ketchup,
你就不会自问那到底是不是肉了
you might not ask yourself if it's really meat.
在给你小男友发短信吗
Texting your boyfriend?
不  是删除他的照片
Huh, deleting his pictures.
男人都烂透了
Guys suck.
你现在才明白这一点吗
You're just figuring that out now?
-发生什么事了  小黛  -他在跟人约会
- What happened, Debs? - He's on a date.
如何才能知道自己是否爱上某人了呢
How can you tell when you're in love with someone?
当你想把那个人的心掏出来
When you wanna rip someone's heart out
重重踩上去  直到它变成浆糊
and stomp on it till it's soup.
那个贱人是谁
So who's the bitch?
贱人
Bitch?
就是那个自己找不到男人
The skank who can't get her own man,
所以来勾搭你的
So she moved onto yours?
你认为这是她的错
You think it's her fault?
她非常清楚自己在做什么
She knows exactly what she's doing.
真替她遗憾
Feel sorry for her.
为什么
Why?
她不知道自己惹的是谁
She doesn't know who she messed with.
黛比·加拉格
Debbie Gallagher.
美国辩护律师
2014会议
芝加哥
我在楼上开了个房
Got a room upstairs.
别拐弯抹角的
You don't beat around the bush.
我知道我要什么  你呢
I know what I want. Do you?
不不  就一杯
No, no, no, no, only one.
-说的跟真的似的  -明天会很累的
- Yeah, right. - Got a big day tomorrow.
得去找个工作
Got to get a job.
你觉得这就是为了你一个人吗
Oh, you think this is just about you?
你是为了我们两个喝的
You drinking for the both of us.
我就像个瘫子  让你去跑马拉松
I'm like a paraplegic telling you to run the marathon
因为我的腿动不了
'cause my legs won't move.
只要这些小崽子们一钻出来
Once these little girls pop out,
我就要补偿我失去的时间
I'm gonna be making up for lost time.
等不到医生把她胳膊从我那啥里拽出来
I'm gonna be downing my first vodka
我就要喝我的第一杯伏特加
before the doctor even pulls her hand out of my hoo-ha.
我肯定会在的
I'll be right there.
你最好在
You better.
只要是白天
As long as it's during daylight hours.
我今天差点错过宵禁
I almost missed my curfew today.
什么
What?
我在找工作
I was looking for a job.
必须得赚钱  帮利普
Gotta make money. You know, gotta help out Lip.
他自己的事已经够多了
You know, he's got so much on his plate.
我不知道他是怎么做到的
I don't know how he's doing it all.
名师出高徒
Well, he learned from the best.
我骗了他
I lied to him.
告诉他已经有戏了
Told him I had some leads.
我唯一能找到工作的地方就是汉堡店
Only job I could find was a burger place.
聊胜于无
Well, minimum wage is better than nothing.
是夜班  想做都不行
It's the night shift. Couldn't even take it.
你应该回去找做杯子的那些人
You could go back to the cuppers.
在他们因为不端行为开除了我之后
After they fired me for misconduct?
对  "麦克  如果你再给我个机会
Yeah, "Hey, Mike, if you give me another chance,
我保证不搞你哥哥  也不犯罪了"
I promise not to screw your brother or commit a felony."
如果他们说你是被裁员的
Well, if they say they downsized you,
你就是失业人员了
You could get unemployment.
我不觉得他们会帮我任何忙
I don't think they're inclined to do me any favors.
问问又不会少块肉
Can't hurt to ask.
我不能回那里去
I can't go back there.
好吧  那加拉格日托呢
All right, what about Gallagher day care?
那总能赚到几块钱
That was always good for a few bucks.
利亚姆
Liam.
没事的
It's okay.
做噩梦了吗
Just a bad dream, huh?
只是个噩梦
Oh, yeah, it's just a bad dream.
没事的
You're okay.
没事
It's okay.
好了  没事了
All right. You're okay.
天堂披萨店
Slice of heaven pizza.
贱人
Skank.
你找安吉吗
You looking for Angie?
不是  新来的那个
No, the new girl.
哦  西玛
Oh, uh, Seema.
她刚刚送外卖回来
Um, she just got back from her deliveries.
等下
Hold on.
西玛  有电话
Hey, Seema, phone.
喂
Hello?
你不知道你惹上谁了  贱人
You don't know who you messed with, skank.
你喜欢玩硬的吗
You like it rough?
看你喜欢什么
Whatever you're into.
说茄子  混账东西
Say cheese, motherfucker!
怎么回事
What the hell?
这是宝格丽
Hey, that's Bulgari.
大概能值200块
That's, like, 200 bucks cash.
表不错  哥们
Nice watch, man.
出什么事了
What's going on?
我要报警了
I'm calling the fucking police.
你试试看
Yeah, you do that.
你觉得克莱尔和小奥拉诺
What do you think Claire and little Eleanor
看到我刚拍的照片会怎么想
would make of the photo I just took?
谁
Who?
谁管他们叫什么
Whatever the fuck their names are.
你要曝光他吗
You're gonna out him?
不得已的话
Only if I have to.
他的错是为人虚伪  对吗
Hey, his fault for living a lie, right?
我们下楼玩玩吧
Why don't we take a little trip downstairs?
先去ATM机
Gonna go to the ATM machine.
如果你要取我的钱
If you're gonna take my money,
至少让这嫩小子给我口
least you can do is have the twink suck me off.
你觉得他就是这样吗  某个嫩小子
That all you think he is? Some twink?
我蛋都憋红了
He gave me blue balls.
是吗
Did he?
现在青一块紫一块了
Now they're black and blue balls.
不好意思
Excuse me.
让一下
Please move.
马蒂
Hey, Matt.
当然  我也想见你
Sure, I'd love to see you again.
明天晚上没问题
Yeah, tomorrow night works.
拜拜
Bye.
西格尔护理学校
上帝啊
Jesus.
你在这儿干吗
What are you doing here?
我的房子怎么了
What happened to my house?
你妈妈呢
Where's your mom?
去给外公换尿布了
Out getting diapers for grandpa.
弗兰克在吗
Is Frank here?
这是你最爱吃的香蕉煎饼
Okay, we got your favorite, banana pancakes.
我喜欢香蕉煎饼
Oh, I love banana pancakes.
那是我的衣服吗
Hey, is that my shirt?
我没带换洗的衣服  所以就
Yeah, I didn't bring a change of clothes, so...
有咖啡吗
You got coffee?
真当自己家了
Oh, make yourself at home.
你有意见吗
You got a problem?
这些钱够了吧  混蛋
This should more than cover the bisquick, asshole.
祝你跟我的小孩抢食抢的开心
Hope you're happy about taking food out of my baby's mouth.
你的孩子怎么样了
Yeah, how is your kid?
我他妈怎么知道
How the fuck should I know?
要去跑步  一起吗
Hey, going for a run. Wanna join?
比起脑内啡[运动后产生的荷尔蒙]
Uh, no, you know, I prefer carcinogens
我更喜欢致癌物
to endorphins.
-你看到菲奥娜了吗  -已经走了
- Hey, you seen Fiona? - Left already.
你有没有想过
Hey, look, you given any thought
重新读高中
to re-enrolling in high school?
我的帽子呢  外面很冷
Where's my hat? It's cold out.
你对游戏怎么看
Hey, what do you think of gaming?
魔兽世界  虚拟人生什么的
World of warcraft, second life?
怎么  你是说玩游戏吗
What, you mean like playing 'em?
不不
No, no.
商业性的一面
The business side of it.
未来属于在线多玩家游戏
Online multiplayer gaming is the future.
我在杂志上读到的
I read all about it in a magazine.
你觉得你会擅长吗
Think you'd be any good at it?
我不知道
I-I don't know.
我觉得这会很棒
Yeah, I think it'd be great.
对于游戏我有一堆点子
I got tons of ideas for games, you know?
在这呢
Here it is.
你确定不要一起跑吗
Hey, you sure you don't wanna join?
八英里
Eight miles.
不  不用了
No, I'm--I'm good.
她是阿三吗
She's a towel-head?
应该是印度人吧
Indian, I think.
原来马蒂喜欢深色人种
Matt likes dark meat.
她晚上还去上护校
Goes to nursing school at night.
好像自己很特别似的
Like she's something special.
她还有自己的公寓呢
Even has her own apartment.
你还跟她回家了  真是变态
You followed her home? Freak.
自他们上次约会后  马蒂就没有给我发短信了
Matty hasn't texted me since their last date.
什么是她有而我没有的
What does she have that I don't?
公寓算不算
An apartment.
他会喜欢她仅仅是因为她年纪大
He's only into her 'cause she's older.
为什么男人都这么在乎性爱
Why do guys care so much about sex?
因为感觉无比爽
Because it feels awesome.
好像你试过似的
Like you would know.
如果我的手跟真逼有那么一点点像
If my hand is anything like the real thing,
那就绝对是爽翻天了
it's off the chain.
你找什么呢
What are you looking for?
我得继续留堂察看
Need to get back into detention.
为什么
Why?
真爱  姐
True love, sis.
屠宰场怎么样
So, uh, how's the slaughterhouse?
一旦习惯了那个味道...
Ha, once you get used to the smell...
我骗谁呢
Who am I kidding?
绝对不可能习惯那个味道的
You never get used to the smell.
我要加班
I get overtime.
那儿有人死了  或者被炒了吗
Any deaths or dismissals?
抱歉
Sorry.
我得送瑞奇去日托
I gotta get Ricky to day care.
我就是为这事来的
Well, that's why I was dropping by.
我在想  也许我能继续照看他
I was thinking maybe I could watch him again.
谢了  但我们现在有地方去
Thanks, but we're set for now.
我比塞马克路那个日托所
Well, I charge a hell of a lot less
便宜多了
than that place over on Cermak.
你就是要去那儿吧
That's where you're going, right?
而且孩子们回家时也不会有虱子和咬痕
And we don't send 'em home with lice and bite marks.
如果事情有变  我再给你电话
I'll give you a call if things change.
瑞奇去年夏天在加拉格日托所过得很开心
Ricky had a great time last summer at Gallagher day care.
嗑药的事怎么样了
How's the drug thing?
就那么一次
It was just that one time.
抱歉  菲奥娜
I'm sorry, Fiona.
丽兹  你曾一整个周末
Liz, you left him at my house
在北郎代尔
for an entire weekend once
往手臂里静注毒品
while you were up in North Lawndale
那时你就把他扔在我家
sticking a needle in your arm.
是啊
Yeah.
我得走了
Gotta go.
我操你妈
Fuck you.
弗兰克
Frank?
Frank!
你现在这个样子
Kinda hard to get mad at you
让我想气你把我的家具都卖了
about selling all my furniture
都气不起来了
when you're like this.
我知道陷入绝境是什么感受
But I know what it's like to have your back against the wall.
我和罗杰·奔跑·树分手了
Roger Running Tree and I broke up.
跟他不适合
It wasn't meant to be.
他有愤怒管理问题
He's got anger issues.
而且联邦政府还在通缉他
Plus he's on the run from the federal government.
好像是冒领补偿金
Something like collecting false reparations.
原来他的印第安血统比我还少
It turns out he has less Indian blood than I do.
他大部分是墨西哥血统
He's mostly Mexican.
但是孩子们  弗兰克
But the children, Frank.
天呐  弗兰克
Oh, my gosh, Frank,
他们太可爱了
they're so adorable.
我和罗杰本来都要结婚
And Roger and I, we were gonna get married
然后收养他们了  结果他露出了真面目
and adopt them before he showed his true colors,
显然  他是棕色皮肤而不是红色
which is evidently brown and not red.
弗兰克  他们无亲无故
Frank, they're alone in the world.
你懂我的意思吗
Do you understand what I'm getting at?
我只需要一纸婚书
All I need is a marriage certificate.
弗兰克  你愿意娶我吗
Frank, will you marry me?
哲学论文写完了吗
Finishing your philosophy paper?
-快了  -最好抓紧时间了
- Yeah. - Better hurry.
两小时后你有场经济学测验呢
You have an econ quiz in two hours.
对了  关于这事
Uh, right, you know, about that,
我不禁注意到这张日程表
I-I couldn't help but notice the schedule.
我给你做的
I made it for you.
我就猜到可能是你
Yeah, no, I thought it might have been you,
你还细分为五分钟一段
and you broke it down into five-minute segments.
谁会在12点55分排上事情啊
I mean, who schedules something for 12:55?
这样你就能更好地管理时间了
So you can better manage your time.
你还预先排出了上厕所的时间
Right, but you even put in preset bathroom breaks.
我同步到你的新手机里了
I synced it to your new phone.
你还给我买了新手机
You got me a new phone?
不用谢
You're welcome.
谢谢
Thank you.
不过说真的  这张日程表
But seriously, this-this schedule, it's just--
不是我的风格
It's--it's not me, okay?
我不习惯连拉屎都要事先安排好
I'm not used to having my dumps planned out in advance.
就是  我不能...
You know, it's--I can't--
我不能这样严格控制我的生活
I can't regiment my life like that, all right?
所以我来帮你控制
That's why I'm doing it for you.
我算是比较...
Okay, I guess I'm just more of a, uh,
潇洒不羁吧
fly by the seat of my pants kind of guy.
那结果怎样呢
How's that working out for you?
不如给爷快速吹个箫
How 'bout a quick BJ then?
还要45分钟才到吹箫时间
BJ break isn't for another 45 minutes.
吹箫时间
你想怎么样
What do you want?
曼迪  她昨晚在这儿吗
Mandy, she here last night?
-她没跟你在一起吗  -没有  我在上班
- She wasn't with you? - No, I was at work.
我往家里打电话没人接
I kept calling the house, no answer.
然后我又打了她的手机  她说在家
Then I call her cell, she say she's at home.
她跟利普在一起吗
She with Lip?
你还会逻辑思考了呀
You just putting two and two together, huh?
不错嘛  爱因斯坦
Hey, good for you, Einstein.
他在这狗窝里吗
He in this motherfucker?
不在  那混蛋在大学
Nah, asshole's at college.
那地方很大  有很多栋楼
It's a big place, lots of buildings.
人们去那里学习  还是算了吧
People go there to learn. Don't worry about it.
-老兄  他学校在哪  -西麦克斯威尔
- Man, where at? - West Maxwell.
你准备把跟曼迪睡过的男人
Hey, you planning on giving a beat down
全揍一顿吗
to every guy Mandy's been with?
你的手臂会累断的
Your arms are gonna get fucking tired.
拉米雷兹校长是卡尔·加拉"各"的走狗
你在干什么
What are you doing?
陈述事实
Stating the obvious.
你为自己争取到了两周的留堂察看
You just bought yourself two more weeks' detention.
棒
Cool.
你把自己的姓拼错了
You know, you misspelled your last name.
加拉"各"的走狗
洛文塔尔新娘用品店吗
Lowenthal Bridal?
我要再婚了
Hi, I'm getting remarried.
谢谢  我太高兴了
Oh, thank you. I'm over the moon about it.
事实上  我22年前就是在你们家
Yeah, um, and actually, I-I bought my wedding dress
买的婚纱
from you 22 years ago.
自那之后我瘦了不少
And since then I've lost a considerable amount of weight.
一点吧
Well, I would say a few.
我
I-- -
我一会再打给你好吗
Uh, can I call you back?
我有件非常重要的事要和你商量一下
I need to talk to you about something very serious.
家具的事我可以解释
I can explain the furniture.
还有那个"出售"牌子和碎了的窗户
And the "For sale" Sign. And the broken window.
你穿淡紫色的衣服好看吗
How do you look in lilac?
你的伴娘装
Your dress.
我想让你当我的伴娘
I want you to be my maid of honor.
伴娘
Maid of honor?
-弗兰克同意了  -什么
- Yes, Frank said yes. - What?
我还订好了教堂
Yes, and I--and I've already booked the church.
我想在这里接待客人
And I--and I thought we could have the reception here.
我考虑把屋子装扮成冬季仙境
And I was thinking of, like, a winter wonderland.
可以飘点雪花
And we would do, like, snowflakes and--
还有白色的木头和灯笼
And white wood and lanterns.
你觉得怎么样
And what do you think?
你的意见非常重要
And, well, your opinion is very important to me
因为我要当你妈妈了
because I'm gonna be your new mom.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
外公好像没有呼吸了
I don't think grandpa's breathing.
-不  -天啊
- No! - Oh, my god!
我提着  我提着
I got it, I got it.
好的
Okay.
爸爸
Dad?
弗兰克你还不能死
Oh, not yet, Frank.
别死
Not yet.
昏过去了  还活着
It's faint, but he's still alive.
打911
Call 911.
欢迎再来
Hey, come again.
伊夫耶尼亚
Yevgeny.
你儿子的名字
Name of your son.
-这什么狗屁名字  -我父亲的
- The fuck kinda name is that? - My father's.
那个为了两百块把你卖了的男的
The one who sold you to a pimp for 200 bucks?
你给儿子取他的名字
You name your kid after him?
是三百  他也有优点
It was 300, and he had good qualities too.
是啊  很明显  我们两清了
Yeah, clearly. We're square.
回你自己的家吧
Come home where you belong.
我们说的可不包括这个
Wasn't part of the deal.
回家吧
Come home.
你他妈再自以为是蹦出半句话
You breathe a fucking word about what you think you know,
我保证让你的孩子没妈
I promise you your kid's gonna be an orphan.
这里不允许家庭暴力
Okay, hey. No domestic abuse.
跟其他人一样去外边解决
Take it outside like everyone else.
回家  否则要你好看
Come home or else.
来吧  帅哥  该你了
Come on, big boy. You're next.
想要一个吗  正在打折
Do you want one? They're on sale.
可能吧  太可爱了
Maybe. They're so cute.
需要帮忙的话叫我
Let me know if I can help with anything.
好的
Okay.
好厉害
Oh, my god.
他在哪
Where is he?
你不能就这么闯进来
You can't just come in here like that.
-加拉格  -谁
- Gallagher. - Who?
宏观经济学
我妻子过来找我  发着抖
So my wife comes to me shaking.
说结婚戒指丢了
Wedding ring's missing.
是女佣偷的  还是吸嗨的时候弄丢的
Cleaning woman? Super?
我拿起电话
I grabbed the phone,
假装报警
pretended to report it to the police.
金融系统分析师
客户经理
我不敢跟她说我把戒指当掉
I didn't have the heart to tell her that I pawned the ring
会计主管
办公室助理
行政文员
换了点毒品
for a few rocks.
最糟糕的是
Worst part?
我一点都没让她尝
I didn't even share any of it with her.
不管怎样  这是...
Look, look, anyway, that was--
是六年前的事了
that was six years ago,
每天我感谢上天自己来到了这里
and every day I thank god that I'm here
而不是待在监狱
instead of back there.
好的  明天同一时间
Okay, same time tomorrow.
谁有法院的单子  过来我签字
If you have a court card, come up and I'll sign it.
但愿我们没有打扰你
Hope we didn't disturb you.
对不起  我不是故意无礼
Sorry, I didn't mean to be rude.
我没有毒瘾
I just--I don't have a drug problem.
不是我觉得自己没有
No, not like I do, but I don't think I do.
是真的没有
I-I really don't.
我只是需要你签个字  然后我可以去找工作
I just need my card signed so I can go look for a job.
或许这两个忙我都可以帮
Might be able to help you with both.
真的吗
Seriously?
资料是公开的  我重罪在身
Full disclosure, I-- I have a felony.
你和这儿百分之九十的人都是
You and 90% of everyone else here.
我因为教唆罪蹲过一年
I did a year for solicitation.
告诉胡安是金介绍你来的
Tell Juan that Kim sent you.
太好了
That is so nice.
这不是去接客吧
It's not hooking, right?
真是接客啊
It is hooking?
为了喂饱孩子的肚子
Puts food on the table for my kids.
离开马蒂
否则下次就是毒蛇
你的留校察看不是已经完了吗
Thought you served your time.
看到外面柜子上的话了吗
You see the lockers?
是你弄的
That was you?
坏蛋就是我
I'm kind of a badass.
想不想找点乐子
You wanna have some fun?
想
Yeah.
没事  我没事
No, I'm fine.
他们在帮你
They're trying to help.
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off of me.
爸爸  求你了
Dad, please.
-需要测血压  -滚开
- Need blood pressure. - Fuck off!
-快点  -滚
- Come on. - Get out!
爸爸  别这样
Dad stop.
先生  我们得把你送到急诊室
Sir, we need to take you to the E.R.
-费雪  数三下  -不  不
- Fisher, on three. - No, no.
-一  二  -我的天
- One, two- - Jesus Christ.
我不想去医院
I do not want to go to the hospital!
先生  你拒绝治疗吗
Sir, are you refusing treatment?
你们要走了
You're leaving?
不能强迫他
Can't force him.
为什么
Well, why?
你个贱人
You bitch!
我觉得你需要帮助
I thought you needed some help.
我真不该去找你
I never should have tried to find you.
别这么说
Don't say that.
怪不得你留不住男人
It's not a mystery that men leave you!
我不想你死
I don't want you to leave!
所以我才把他们叫来
That's why I called them!
我不想你死
I don't want you to leave!
好吧
Okay.
我不知道该怎么办了
I don't know what else to do.
给我点止痛药
Something for the pain, please.
别动
Don't move.
我马上就来
I will be right back.
是洛温塔尔婚纱店吗
Yeah, Lowenthal Bridal?
我是希拉·杰克森
Yeah, it's Sheila Jackson.
我需要将婚礼提前
Yeah, I need to move the wedding up.
我可以快点拿到婚纱吗
Is there any way I could get the dress sooner?
明天如何
How 'bout tomorrow?
恩格斯是天才
Engels, a genius?
更像是马克思的捧友
More like Marx's glorified butt buddy.
有只愤怒的黑牛找你去了
该死
Shit.
靠  拿着
Shit, hold this.
有关全球变暖的10个真相
加入战斗  不再漠视
我干什么了
What'd I do?
-干了曼迪  -我没有
- Mandy! - No, I didn't!
好吧  我承认
Ow, fuck! All right, okay!
但只有一次
Okay, just-- just once though.
-死过来  -操
- Come here! - Shit!
不喜欢那个答案吗
Okay, you didn't want that answer?
让一让  让一让
Excuse me, excuse me.
好了  听着
All right, look,
我跟她已经结束了 彻底结束了
we're done though. We're done.
好吗  我有新女朋友了
Okay? All right, I got a girlfriend.
也许我该像你一样干了你的女朋友
Maybe I should do yours like you did mine.
可以  但只能从菊花入
Okay, but only in the ass, all right?
-她很珍惜自己  -去你妈的
- She's saving herself. - Fuck that.
操
Shit.
滚过来
Come here.
放开他  放开他
Get off him! Get off!
-好吧  好吧  -别发疯了
- All right, all right. - Knock it off.
学生证拿出来看看
Let's see some I.D. both of you.
你是这里的学生吗
You go to school here?
听着  我不认识他  警官
Look, I don't--I don't know him, officers, okay?
他就这么...
You know, he just--
他问我  要不要买可卡因
He asked if I wanted to buy any crack,
-我说不要  然后...  -操你妈的
- and when I said no... - Fuck you!
那我们现在干嘛
Uh, so what do you wanna do?
我能弄到一些爆竹和汽油
I can get my hands on some firecrackers and gasoline.
酷毙了  我玩过冲锋枪
Cool. I shot a Mac-10 before.
但从没碰过手枪
But never one of those.
是假的
It's fake.
看着不像
Looks real.
要是能看出来怎么能唬住店员
Need it to if we're gonna get the guy behind the counter
把收银机里的钱都交出来
to give us all the money in the register.
你不用跟来  我自己能行
Don't have to. I can do it alone.
不  我没问题
No, I can do it.
你确定你准备好出演你的打劫处女秀了吗
Sure you're ready to pop your armed robbery cherry?
确定  早干过几百次了
Yeah, I've done it lots of times before.
你真可爱  黑色还是迷彩
You're cute. Black or camo?
菲奥娜  你好
Fiona, hi.
没收到最后一张支票吗
Did you not get your last check?
收到了
No, I-I did.
有点事  想请你帮忙
I have a favor to ask you.
说吧
Sure.
你还好吗
How you holding up?
以前比较好
I've been better.
我在想...  能不能
I was wondering if, uh,
把我的因工作失误开除
instead of being fired for misconduct,
弄成是公司裁员的样子
you could make it so that I was downsized?
我不...
I don't--
如果有别的选择  我不会开口问的
I wouldn't ask if I had any other options.
让我看看你能不能帮你
Let me see what I can do.
你真是胆大包天
You have a hell of a lot of nerve.
当哥把你领进门的时候
You know, I-I-I withheld judgment
我对你没有偏见
when my brother brought you home.
我告诉自己  "人的出身高低
I said to myself, "She can't help where she came from,
成长环境以及父母都不是自己选的”
how she was raised, who her parents are."
我父母邀请你进入我家
My mom and dad invited you into their home.
让你与全家人一起坐着吃饭
They let you sit at their table with our family,
作为回报  你毁了麦克
and in return you destroyed Mike.
毁了我们全家
All of us.
现在你还敢来这里  问我们
And now you come here and you ask
愿不愿意为你向联邦政府撒谎
if we will lie for you to the federal government.
你以为自己是个好人
You think that you're a good person.
但你不是
You're not.
去毁你自己的家庭吧
Destroy your own family.
别祸害我的
And leave mine alone.
把收银机里的钱都交出来
Empty the register!
开玩笑呢是吧
Is this a joke?
现金交出来  快点
The cash! Now!
是的  好吧
Yeah, okay.
我会把我的钱都交给
Yeah, I'm just gonna hand over my money
你们两个小矮人
to the lollipop guild.
我操
Whoa, shit!
-我去  -包拿来
- Holy fuck. - Get the bag.
我错了  好吗
Sorry. Okay?
拿走
Take it.
你不是说是假的吗
You said it was fake.
你真该看看当时自己的表情
You should have seen your face.
我们抢了多少钱
How much we get?
你留着吧
You keep it.
太劲爆了
That was awesome.
那个男的好像吓出屎来了
I think that guy crapped his pants.
明天  去抢银行吧
Tomorrow let's hit a bank.
找到加拉格了吗
Hey, you find Gallagher?
懂不懂礼貌  混蛋
Yeah, excuse you, asshole.
你看不看小孩
You watch baby?
不看
No.
你看个屁
The fuck you looking at?
马蒂  今晚有活动吗
Hey, Matty, what are you up to tonight?
如果有空  给我打电话
Thought you might be free. Call me.
我才不在乎
I don't give a shit
你是不是还在玩布娃娃的十岁毛孩
if you're ten years old and playing with dolls.
你想开战  现在我们开战了
You want a war, you got it.
你不知道自己惹上了什么人  婊子
You don't know who you messed with, bitch.
醒着吗
You awake?
楼下有人等你
Guys are asking for you downstairs.
什么人
What guys?
来了  他来了
Here we go. He's coming.
好了  别说了
Okay, shh, shh, shh.
快过来  弗兰克
Get your ass down here, Frank.
搞什么
What is this?
没法带你去酒吧
Couldn't bring you to the bar.
所以就把酒吧给你搬来了
So we brought the bar to you.
就算是变态杀人狂也会有最后的晚餐
Even John Wayne Gacy got a last meal.
交给你们了  行吗
Got him, fellas?
交给我们吧  美妞
We got him, doll. Here.
快过来坐下  弗兰克  来吧
Get your ass over here, Frank. Come on.
这里有些东西是给你准备的
We got something over here for you.
是啊  快坐下  兄弟
Yeah. Have a seat, man.
-好样的  -坐好了
- Attboy. - There you go.
这杯都是沫沫的啤酒是给你的
Got a frosty brew for you here.
喝不了
Can't.
是不含酒精的
It's non-alcoholic.
把这个加在有生之年没想到能看见之事的列表上
Add that to the list of things I thought I'd never see.
奥巴马的出生证明
Obama's birth certificate,
弗兰克喝无酒精啤酒
and now Frank drinking O'Doul's.
别告诉你相信那张证明是真的
Oh, please, don't tell me you're buying that forgery.
人家公证过了
It was certified!
公证有个屁用  我是阿普尓顿人
It was certified? I'm from Kenosha.
我能在20分钟之内
I could have a certified Hawaii birth certificate
-搞到夏威夷的出生证明  -你从不相信别人
- sent here in 20 minutes. - You are never convinced.
我应该告诉警察毒品是你的
I shoulda told the fucking cops thait was you!
-应该告诉警察的  -你没事吧
- I shoulda told them it was you! - Hey, hey, all right.
本来一切都很好  现在全毁了
Everything was great, and now it's fucked!
都是因为你
Everything is fucked because of you.